Marcio Augusto Lubeke

APARTMENT 10 - KINGSGLADE CRADDOCKSTOWN COURT NAAS - CO. KILDARE - W91 WN26 +353 89 943 6759

mlubeke@gmail.com

44 years old · Italo-Brazilian · Married
Willingness to travel

OBJECTIVE: ENGINEERING

QUALIFICATIONS SUMMARY

Career being developed in the area of Civil Engineering, with experience in monitoring, planning and control of works, surveys, assistance in the preparation of physical-financial schedule, assistance in budget spreadsheets, acting according to the costs and deadlines established by the organization.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

01/06/2022 - 08/08/2022 - Gamma Building Services Ltd. - Ireland

Mediun Company

GENERAL OPERATIVES / FITTER GLASS / CONSTRUCTION MANAGER

08/08/2022 - 14/01/2023 - Kepak Group

Big Company

GENERAL OPERATIVES

01/06/2022 - 08/08/2022 - Gamma Building Services Ltd. - Ireland

Mediun Company

GENERAL OPERATIVES / FITTER GLASS / CONSTRUCTION MANAGER

25/04/2022 - 01/06/2022 - Warehouse for Kaizen Recruitment - Ireland

Large Company

GENERAL OPERATIVES

15/12/2021 - (24/04/2021) - Stella Cine (Group Press up) - Ireland

Large Company

CLEANER

15/06/2020 - 01/09/2021 - Spalla Engenharia Eireli - Brazil

Medium-sized Company in the segment of construction in public and Private works.

Civil Engineer

01/11/2020 - 05/04/2021 - Tower Engenharia e Construção Ltda - Brazil

Medium / Large Company in the segment of constructions in public works.

Civil Engineer

01/03/2020 - 01/10/2020 - Dekton Engenharia e Construção Ltda / Construtora Armada Eireli - Brazil Small / Medium-sized Company of the segment of constructions in public works.

Civil Engineer

01/01/2018 - (Web Acting) - Mtek Tower Engenharia e Construção Ltda - Brazil

Small Business in the construction, renovation and report segment.

Director and Civil Engineer

01/01/2018 - 01/09/2019 - **Dekton Engenharia e Construção Ltda / Construtora Armada Eireli - Brazil** *Small / Medium-sized Company of the segment of constructions in public works.*

Civil Engineer

28/09/2015 - 31/12/2017 - **Dekton Engenharia e Construção Ltda / Construtora Armada Eireli - Brazil**Small / Medium-sized Company of the segment of constructions in public works.

Civil Engineering Assistant

02/01/2000 - 25/09/2015 - Acting as Teacher and Personal Trainner.

- Developing skills in the realization of budgets, measurements, photographic reports, as well as in the
 preparation of technical reports, evaluating the available resources and procedures most appropriate
 to the type of project conducted;
- Developing skills in metal constructions such as sheds, supermarkets, among others,
- Ability to fill out the journal of works;

- People management, working in the distribution of tasks, allocation of labor, performance evaluation and delivery of guidance, seeking the formation of skilled teams aligned with the achievement of goals.
- Responsible for the requisition and control of the receipt of materials and equipment of the works, ability to purchase materials and rental of machinery, thus acting in the quantitative survey, valuing the good progress of activities.
- Assistance in structuring the monthly expenses forecast, data analysis and issuance of technical reports, passing strategic information to the Board, contributing to decision making.
- Experience in the planning and execution of constructions, expansions and renovations, also working in the realization of studies of characteristics and specifications for guidance of works, focusing on meeting the established schedules.
- Assistance in conducting technical reports and surveys.
- · Acting in bids and registration minutes

EDUCATION

GRADUATED AND POST-GRADUATED IN PHYSICAL EDUCATION - **UNIBAN**GRADUATED IN CIVIL ENGINEERING - **UNITED METROPOLITAN COLLEGE - FMU**

COMPLEMENTARY TRAINING

SEVERAL COURSES IN THE AREA OF COORDINATION AND/OR TEAMWORK;

- TECHNICAL DESIGN DIGICAD SCHOOL;
- AUTOCAD 2D DIGICAD SCHOOL;
- EXCEL FOR ENGINEERS DIGICAD SCHOOL;
- CONSTRUCTION WASTE MANAGEMENT FMU;
- EXTRA ACTIVITIES CURRICULARS AT FMU: CONSTRUCTION SITE, SLUMP TEST AND CONCRETE PROOF BODY, PROCEDURES FOR RECEIVING CONCRETE, TRUCK CUBICAGE, AMONG OTHERS;
- COURSE "INTRODUCTION TO CIVIL CONSTRUCTION" (WORKLOAD 104Hs);
- Course of "Construction Techniques" (workload 40hs);
- COURSE "MANAGEMENT AND SUPERVISION OF WORKS, PROJECTS AND POSTURES (WORKLOAD 96HS);
- COURSE "FIRST STEPS WITH REVIT" (WORKLOAD 10HS) LB FERNANDES.
- MASTER IN REINFORCED CONCRETE (DURATION OF 12 MONTHS) PROF. RANGEL LAGE
- CONSTRUCTION COURSE IN METAL STRUCTURES AND WELDS.
- Manual Handling.

LANGUAGES

English - Basic

COMPUTER

- OFFICE SUITE;
- INTERMEDIATE KNOWLEDGE IN EXCEL;
- INTERNET;
- WOW ADVANCED;
- AUTOCAD 2D